MIT
just
tested
AI
agents
on
real-world
tasks.
Not
toy
benchmarks.
Real
tasks.
Filing
taxes,
booking
flights,
managing
spreadsheets.
Every
single
one
failed.
The
best
agent
completed
just
43%
of
tasks.
The
worst?
Under
10%.
And
here's
the
scary
part.
These
are
the
agents
companies
are
selling
you
right
now.
The
ones
claiming
to
replace
your
entire
workforce.
MIT
found
they
break
on
simple
things
Pop-up
windows
Changed
layouts,
multi-step
forms
The
kind
of
stuff
a
human
handles
without
thinking
AI
agents
aren't
ready
Not
even
close
So
the
next
time
someone
tries
to
sell
you
a
fully
autonomous
AI
worker
Show
them
this
study
Follow
for
more
AI
reality
checks